data = [{
			"question" : "What is the name of the largest star of the world ever discovered by human?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "UY Scuti",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"KW Sagitarii",
				"V354 Cephei",
				"Sun"
			]
		},		{
			"question" : "When the moon appears darkened as it passes into the earth's shadow?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Lunar Eclipse",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Moon Eclipse",
				"Apocalyps",
				"Solar Eclipse"
			]
		},		{
			"question" : "What is the most precious material of the world?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Antimatter",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Diamond",
				"Californium",
				"Dark-matter"
			]
		},		{
			"question" : "Which planet is called the sister of earth?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Venus",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Mars",
				"Saturn",
				"Jupiter"
			]
		},		{
			"question" : "Which is the largest animal ever lived on earth?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Blue Whale",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"",
				"Argentinosorus",
				"Titanoboa"
				"Megalodon"
			]
		
		},
			"question" : "Which is the slowest animal?",
			"category" : "generalKnowledge",
			"subCategory" : "null",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Sloth",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Snail",
				"Lobster",
				"Tortoise"
			]
		},
			{
			"question" : "How many elements are there in a periodic table?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "chem",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "118",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"121",
				"120",
				"119"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What's called the process of producing Food in Plants?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "biology",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Photosynthesis",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Phosphorylation",
				"Pollination",
				"Osmosis"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "How many phenomenons of light occurs when light is sent from one medium to another?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "physics",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "3",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"2",
				"4",
				"5"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "What type of wave is light?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "physics",
			"difficulty" : "easy",
			"answer" : "Electromagnetic",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Mechanical",
				"Gravitational",
				"Light is not a wave"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "How many types of hydrocarbon are there?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "chemistry",
			"difficulty" : "medium",
			"answer" : "2",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"3",
				"4",
				"5"
			]
		},
		{
			"question" : "Which one is an impossible hydrocarbon?",
			"category" : "science",
			"subCategory" : "chemistry",
			"difficulty" : "medium",
			"answer" : "Methene",
			"otherOptions" : [
				"Methane",
				"Ethane",
				"Ethene"
			]
		}
	]
